Contact

omar.drljevic@mail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/omar-drljevi %C4%87-137710160 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript
Python (Programming Language)
Machine Learning

Omar Drljević

Data Scientist at 73lab

Summary

Experienced Full Stack Engineer and Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python, JavaScript, Machine Learning, HTML and other Web technologies. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from University of Buckingham and proficiency in English.

Experience

73lab
Data Scientist
August 2019 - Present

Info Studio d.o.o.

1 year 7 months

Software Engineer

September 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Software Engineer Intern March 2018 - September 2018 (7 months) Sarajevo

InnoTech Software Engineer June 2016 - September 2016 (4 months) Sarajevo

Education

Sarajevo School of Scinece and Technology Bachelor's degree, Computer Science (2015 - 2019)

University of Buckingham

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)

University of Erlangen-Nuremberg Computer Science